let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "I wanted a green shirt but they only had .....",
    answer: " a white one",
    options: [
      "A) a one white",
      "B) one white",
      "C) a white",
      "D) a white one",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "He ..... never been to America.",
    answer: "B) has",
    options: [
      "A) does",
      "B) has",
      "C) haven't",
      "D) hadn't",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The house was empty. There ..... there.",
    answer: "D)  was nobody",
    options: [
      "A) wasn't nobody",
      "B)  was anybody",
      "C)  was somebody",
      "D)  was nobody",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "If I were rich, I ..... buy a house on the beach.",
    answer: "B) would",
    options: [
      "A) will",
      "B) would",
      "C) should",
      "D) wish",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "When she arrived, he .....",
    answer: "C)  had already left",
    options: [
      "A) already left",
      "B)  has already left",
      "C)  had already left",
      "D)  left",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "I forgot ..... the lights before I left.",
    answer: "A)to turn off",
    options: [
      "A)to turn off",
      "B) put off",
      "C) turning off",
      "D) shot",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "By the time you finish the class I .....",
    answer: "A) will have left",
    options: [
      "A) will have left",
      "B)  leave",
      "C)  going to leave",
      "D)  would left",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The room can't be dirty she .....",
    answer: "D) has just cleaned it.",
    options: [
      "A) is just clean it.",
      "B) have just cleaned it.",
      "C) just clean it.",
      "D) has just cleaned it.",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "He plays soccer, ..... ?",
    answer: "D) doesn't he?",
    options: [
      "A) don't he?",
      "B) does he?",
      "C) isn't he?",
      "D) doesn't he?",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If only I ..... to the party instead of staying at home.",
    answer: "B)  had gone",
    options: [
      "A)  went",
      "B)  had gone",
      "C)  did go",
      "D)  have gone",
    ]
  },
];